<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<course format="html">
  <!-- Begin Chapter -->
 
      <question>
        <text>Access and _____ shall be provided and maintained about all electrical equipment to permit ready and safe operation and maintenance of such equipment.</text>
        <showAfterPage>2</showAfterPage>
        <answer>ventilation</answer>
        <answer>cleanliness</answer>
        <answer>circulation</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[working space]]></answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>Equipment associated with the electrical installation can be located above or below other electrical equipment within their working space when the associated equipment does not extend more than _____ from the front of the electrical equipment.</text>
        <showAfterPage>3</showAfterPage>
        <answer>3 in.</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[6 in.]]></answer>
        <answer>12 in.</answer>
        <answer>30 in.</answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>The minimum height of working spaces about electrical equipment, switchboards, panelboards, or motor control centers operating at 600V, nominal, or less and likely to require examination, adjustment, servicing, or maintenance while energized shall be 6 1/2 ft or the height of the equipment, whichever is greater, except for service equipment or panelboards in existing dwelling units that do not exceed 200A.</text>
        <showAfterPage>4</showAfterPage>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[True]]></answer>
        <answer>False</answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>Illumination shall be provided for all working spaces about service equipment, switchboards, panelboards, and motor control centers _____.</text>
        <showAfterPage>5</showAfterPage>
        <answer>over 600V</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[located indoors]]></answer>
        <answer>rated 1,200A or more</answer>
        <answer>using automatic means of control</answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>The minimum height of dedicated equipment space for motor control centers installed indoors is _____above the enclosure.</text>
        <showAfterPage>6</showAfterPage>
        <answer>3 ft</answer>
        <answer>5 ft</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[6 ft]]></answer>
        <answer>6 1/2 ft</answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>The dedicated space above a panelboard extends to a dropped or suspended ceiling, which is considered a structural ceiling.</text>
        <showAfterPage>7</showAfterPage>
        <answer>True</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[False]]></answer>
      </question>
 
      <question>
        <text>Each multiwire branch circuit shall be provided with a means that will simultaneously disconnect all _____ conductors at the point where the branch circuit originates.</text>
        <showAfterPage>2</showAfterPage>
        <answer>circuit</answer>
        <answer>grounded</answer>
        <answer>grounding</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[ungrounded]]></answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>The ungrounded and grounded conductors of each _____ shall be grouped by cable ties or similar means at each location that terminations, connections, or splices are made.</text>
        <showAfterPage>3</showAfterPage>
        <answer>branch circuit</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[multiwire branch circuit]]></answer>
        <answer>feeder circuit</answer>
        <answer>service-entrance conductor</answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>Where more than one nominal voltage system supplies branch circuits in a building, each _____ conductor of a branch circuit shall be identified by phase and system at all termination, connection, and splice points.</text>
        <showAfterPage>4</showAfterPage>
        <answer>grounded</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[ungrounded]]></answer>
        <answer>grounding</answer>
        <answer>all of these</answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>The GFCI protection required by 210.8(a) and (b) must be _____.</text>
        <showAfterPage>5</showAfterPage>
        <answer>the circuit breaker type only</answer>
        <answer>accessible</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[readily accessible]]></answer>
        <answer>concealed</answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>All 15A and 20A, 125V receptacles located outdoors of dwelling units, including receptacles installed under the eaves of roofs, must be GFCI protected except for a receptacle that’s supplied by a branch circuit dedicated to _____ if the receptacle isn’t readily accessible and the equipment or receptacle has ground-fault protection of equipment (GFPE) [426.28].</text>
        <showAfterPage>6</showAfterPage>
        <answer>fixed electric snow-melting or deicing equipment </answer>
        <answer>pipeline and vessel heating equipment</answer>
        <answer>holiday decorative lighting</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[fixed electric snow-melting or deicing equipment or pipeline and vessel heating equipment]]></answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>GFCI protection shall be provided for all 15A and 20A, 125V receptacles installed within 6 ft of all dwelling unit sinks located in areas other than the _____.</text>
        <showAfterPage>7</showAfterPage>
        <answer>laundry room</answer>
        <answer>bathroom</answer>
        <answer>den</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[kitchen]]></answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>All 15A and 20A, 125V receptacles located outdoors or on rooftops in locations other than dwelling units must be GFCI protected except for a receptacle that’s supplied by a branch circuit dedicated to _____, if the receptacle isn’t readily accessible and the equipment or receptacle has ground-fault protection of equipment (GFPE) [426.28].</text>
        <showAfterPage>8</showAfterPage>
        <answer>fixed electric snow-melting or deicing equipment </answer>
        <answer>pipeline and vessel heating equipment</answer>
        <answer>holiday decorative lighting</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[fixed electric snow-melting or deicing equipment or pipeline and vessel heating equipment]]></answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>All 15A and 20A, 125V receptacles installed within 6 ft of the outside edge of a sink in locations other than dwelling units must be _____.</text>
        <showAfterPage>9</showAfterPage>
        <answer>AFCI protected</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[GFCI protected]]></answer>
        <answer>tamperproof</answer>
        <answer>AFCI protected and GFCI protected</answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>All 15A and 20A, 125V receptacles installed indoors in wet locations must be GFCI protected.</text>
        <showAfterPage>10</showAfterPage>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[True]]></answer>
        <answer>False</answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>All 15A and 20A, 125V receptacles installed in locker rooms with associated showering facilities must be GFCI protected.</text>
        <showAfterPage>11</showAfterPage>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[True]]></answer>
        <answer>False</answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>All 15A and 20A, 125V receptacles installed in garages, service bays, and similar areas where _____ are to be used must be GFCI protected.</text>
        <showAfterPage>12</showAfterPage>
        <answer>electrical diagnostic equipment</answer>
        <answer>electrical hand tools </answer>
        <answer>portable lighting equipment</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[any of these]]></answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>The 2008 NEC introduced an allowance for grounded conductors to be sized at 100 percent of the continuous load, as opposed to the traditional _____ percent for both feeder circuits and branch circuits.</text>
        <showAfterPage>13</showAfterPage>
        <answer>110</answer>
        <answer>115</answer>
        <answer>120</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[125]]></answer>
      </question>
 
      <question>
        <text>Overhead feeder conductors shall have a minimum _____ vertical clearance over residential property and driveways, as well as those commercial areas not subject to truck traffic, where the voltage is limited to 300 volts-to-ground.</text>
        <showAfterPage>2</showAfterPage>
        <answer>10 ft</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[12 ft]]></answer>
        <answer>15 ft</answer>
        <answer>18 ft</answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>The minimum clearance for overhead feeder conductors not exceeding 600V that pass over commercial areas subject to truck traffic is _____.</text>
        <showAfterPage>3</showAfterPage>
        <answer>10 ft</answer>
        <answer>12 ft</answer>
        <answer>15 ft</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[18 ft]]></answer>
      </question>
 
      <question>
        <text>Feeder tap conductors up to 10 ft long are permitted without overcurrent protection at the tap location if the tap conductors comply with the following requirement:</text>
        <showAfterPage>2</showAfterPage>
        <answer>The tap conductors must not extend beyond the equipment they supply</answer>
        <answer>The tap conductors are installed in a raceway if they leave the enclosure</answer>
        <answer>The ampacity of the tap conductor must not be less than the calculated load</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[all of these]]></answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>If the tap conductors leave the enclosure or vault in which the tap is made, the tap conductors must have an ampacity not less than _____ of the rating of the overcurrent device that protects the feeder.</text>
        <showAfterPage>3</showAfterPage>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[1/10th]]></answer>
        <answer>1/8th</answer>
        <answer>1/4th</answer>
        <answer>1/2</answer>
      </question>
 
      <question>
        <text>A conductor on the supply side of a service or within a service equipment enclosure or separately derived system to ensure the electrical conductivity between metal parts required to be electrically connected is known as the _____. </text>
        <showAfterPage>2</showAfterPage>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[supply-side bonding jumper]]></answer>
        <answer>ungrounded conductor</answer>
        <answer>the electrical supply source</answer>
        <answer>grounding electrode conductor</answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>An important consideration for limiting imposed voltage on electrical systems is to remember that bonding and grounding electrode conductors shouldn’t be any longer than necessary and unnecessary bends and loops should be avoided.</text>
        <showAfterPage>3</showAfterPage>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[True]]></answer>
        <answer>False</answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>The grounded conductor of an alternating-current system operating at less than 1,000V shall be routed with the ungrounded conductors and connected to each disconnecting means grounded conductor terminal or bus, which is then connected to the service disconnecting means enclosure via a(n) _____ that’s installed between the service neutral conductor and the service disconnecting means enclosure.</text>
        <showAfterPage>4</showAfterPage>
        <answer>equipment bonding conductor</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[main bonding jumper]]></answer>
        <answer>grounding electrode</answer>
        <answer>intersystem bonding terminal</answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>The grounded conductor brought to service equipment shall be routed with the phase conductors and shall not be smaller than specified in Table _____ when the service-entrance conductors are 1,100 kcmil copper and smaller.</text>
        <showAfterPage>5</showAfterPage>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[250.66]]></answer>
        <answer>250.122</answer>
        <answer>310.16</answer>
        <answer>430.52</answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>Where service-entrance phase conductors are installed in parallel in two or more raceways, the size of the grounded conductor in each race-way shall be based on the total circular mil area of the parallel ungrounded service-entrance conductor in the raceway, sized per 250.24(C)(1), but not smaller than _____.</text>
        <showAfterPage>6</showAfterPage>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[1/0 AWG]]></answer>
        <answer>2/0 AWG</answer>
        <answer>3/0 AWG</answer>
        <answer>4/0 AWG</answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>A grounded conductor shall not be connected to normally noncurrent-carrying metal parts of equipment on the _____ side of the system bond-ing jumper of a separately derived system except as otherwise permitted in Article 250.</text>
        <showAfterPage>7</showAfterPage>
        <answer>supply</answer>
        <answer>grounded</answer>
        <answer>high-voltage</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[load]]></answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>An unspliced _____ that is sized based on the derived phase conductors shall be used to connect the grounded conductor and the supply-side bonding jumper, or the equipment grounding conductor, or both, at a separately derived system.</text>
        <showAfterPage>8</showAfterPage>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[system bonding jumper]]></answer>
        <answer>equipment grounding conductor</answer>
        <answer>grounded conductor</answer>
        <answer>grounding electrode conductor</answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>Where a supply-side bonding jumper of the wire type is run with the derived phase conductors from the source of a separately derived system to the first disconnecting means, it shall be sized in accordance with 250.102(C), based on _____.</text>
        <showAfterPage>9</showAfterPage>
        <answer>the size of the primary conductors</answer>
        <answer>the size of the secondary overcurrent protection</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[the size of the derived phase conductors]]></answer>
        <answer>one-third the size of the primary grounded conductor</answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>The grounding electrode for a separately derived system shall be as near as practicable to, and preferably in the same area as, the grounding electrode conductor connection to the system.</text>
        <showAfterPage>10</showAfterPage>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[True]]></answer>
        <answer>False</answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>For a single separately derived system, the grounding electrode conductor connects the grounded conductor of the derived system to the grounding electrode at the same point on the separately derived system where the _____ is connected.</text>
        <showAfterPage>11</showAfterPage>
        <answer>metering equipment</answer>
        <answer>transfer switch</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[system bonding jumper]]></answer>
        <answer>largest circuit breaker</answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>The common grounding electrode conductor installed for multiple separately derived systems shall not be smaller than _____ copper when using a wire-type conductor.</text>
        <showAfterPage>12</showAfterPage>
        <answer>1/0 AWG</answer>
        <answer>2/0 AWG</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[3/0 AWG]]></answer>
        <answer>4/0 AWG</answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>Each tap conductor to a common grounding electrode conductor for multiple separately derived systems shall be sized in accordance with _____, based on the derived phase conductors of the separately derived system it serves.</text>
        <showAfterPage>13</showAfterPage>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[250.66]]></answer>
        <answer>250.118</answer>
        <answer>250.122</answer>
        <answer>310.15</answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>In an area served by a separately derived system, the _____ shall be connected to the grounded conductor of the separately derived system.</text>
        <showAfterPage>14</showAfterPage>
        <answer>structural steel</answer>
        <answer>metal piping</answer>
        <answer>metal building skin</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[structural steel and metal piping]]></answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>When supplying a grounded system at a separate building or structure, an equipment grounding conductor shall be run with the supply conductors and connected to the building or structure disconnecting means.</text>
        <showAfterPage>15</showAfterPage>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[True]]></answer>
        <answer>False</answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>For a separate building or structure supplied by a separately derived system when overcurrent protection is provided where the conductors originate, the supply conductors must contain a(n) _____.</text>
        <showAfterPage>16</showAfterPage>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[equipment grounding conductor]]></answer>
        <answer>copper conductors only</answer>
        <answer>GFCI protection for the feeder</answer>
        <answer>all of these</answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>In order for a metal underground water pipe to be used as a grounding electrode, it shall be in direct contact with the earth for _____.</text>
        <showAfterPage>17</showAfterPage>
        <answer>5 ft</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[10 ft or more]]></answer>
        <answer>less than 10 ft</answer>
        <answer>20 ft or more</answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>The metal frame of a building shall be considered a grounding electrode where one of the NEC-prescribed methods for connection of the metal frame to earth has been met:</text>
        <showAfterPage>18</showAfterPage>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[True]]></answer>
        <answer>False</answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>A ground ring consisting of at least _____of bare copper conductor not smaller than 2 AWG buried in the earth encircling a building/structure, can serve as a grounding electrode.</text>
        <showAfterPage>19</showAfterPage>
        <answer>10 ft</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[20 ft]]></answer>
        <answer>30 ft</answer>
        <answer>40 ft</answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>Where used outside, aluminum or copper-clad aluminum grounding electrode conductors shall not be terminated within _____ of the earth.</text>
        <showAfterPage>20</showAfterPage>
        <answer>6 in.</answer>
        <answer>12 in.</answer>
        <answer>15 in.</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[18 in.]]></answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>Grounding electrode conductors shall be installed in one continuous length without a splice or joint, unless spliced _____.</text>
        <showAfterPage>21</showAfterPage>
        <answer>by connecting together sections of a busbar</answer>
        <answer>by irreversible compression-type connectors listed as grounding and bonding equipment</answer>
        <answer>by the exothermic welding process</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[any of these]]></answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>Where service equipment consists of more than one enclosure, grounding electrode connections shall be permitted to be _____.</text>
        <showAfterPage>22</showAfterPage>
        <answer>multiple individual grounding electrode conductors</answer>
        <answer>one grounding electrode conductor at a common location</answer>
        <answer>common grounding electrode conductor and taps.</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[any of these]]></answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>Ferrous metal enclosures for grounding electrode conductors shall be electrically continuous, from the point of attachment to cabinets or equipment, to the grounding electrode.</text>
        <showAfterPage>23</showAfterPage>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[True]]></answer>
        <answer>False</answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>A grounding electrode conductor shall be permitted to be run to any convenient grounding electrode available in the grounding electrode system where the other electrodes, if any, are connected by bonding jumpers per 250.53(C).</text>
        <showAfterPage>24</showAfterPage>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[True]]></answer>
        <answer>False</answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>A means external to enclosures for connecting intersystem _____ conductors shall be provided at service equipment or metering equipment enclosure and disconnecting means of buildings or structures supplied by a feeder.</text>
        <showAfterPage>25</showAfterPage>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[bonding]]></answer>
        <answer>ungrounded</answer>
        <answer>secondary</answer>
        <answer>bonding and ungrounded</answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>At existing buildings or structures, an intersystem bonding termination is not required if other acceptable means of bonding exits. An external accessible means for bonding communications systems together can be by the use of a _____.</text>
        <showAfterPage>26</showAfterPage>
        <answer>nonflexible metallic raceway</answer>
        <answer>grounding electrode conductor</answer>
        <answer>connection approved by the authority having jurisdiction</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[any of these]]></answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>Exposed structural metal that forms a metal building frame that’s likely to become energized must be bonded to the _____.</text>
        <showAfterPage>27</showAfterPage>
        <answer>Service equipment enclosure</answer>
        <answer>Service neutral conductor</answer>
        <answer>Grounding electrode system</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[all of these]]></answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>The nearest available point of the metal water piping system in the area served by a separately derived system must be bonded to the neutral point of the separately derived system where the grounding electrode conductor is connected.</text>
        <showAfterPage>28</showAfterPage>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[True]]></answer>
        <answer>False</answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>Where conductors are run in parallel in multiple raceways or cables and include an EGC of the wire type, the equipment grounding conductor must be installed with each parallel conductor, sized in compliance with 250.122.</text>
        <showAfterPage>29</showAfterPage>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[True]]></answer>
        <answer>False</answer>
      </question>
 
      <question>
        <text>Conductors of ac and dc circuits, rated 600V or less, shall be permitted to occupy the same _____ provided that all conductors have an insulation rating equal to the maximum voltage applied to any conductor.</text>
        <showAfterPage>2</showAfterPage>
        <answer>enclosure</answer>
        <answer>cable</answer>
        <answer>raceway</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[all of these]]></answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>_____ communications wiring must be separated from power and lighting circuits so the higher-voltage conductors don’t accidentally energize them.</text>
        <showAfterPage>3</showAfterPage>
        <answer>Control</answer>
        <answer>Signal</answer>
        <answer>Communications</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[all of these]]></answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>Type MC Cable listed for _____ is permitted to be installed underground under a building without installation in a raceway.</text>
        <showAfterPage>4</showAfterPage>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[direct burial]]></answer>
        <answer>damp and wet locations</answer>
        <answer>rough service</answer>
        <answer>damp and wet locations and rough service</answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>Each direct-buried single conductor cable must be located _____ in the trench to the other single conductor cables in the same parallel set of conductors, including equipment grounding conductors.</text>
        <showAfterPage>5</showAfterPage>
        <answer>perpendicular</answer>
        <answer>bundled together</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[in close proximity]]></answer>
        <answer>spaced apart</answer>
      </question>
 
       <question>
        <text>The ampacities listed in the Tables of Article 310.15(B)(6) do not take _____ into consideration.</text>
        <showAfterPage>2</showAfterPage>
        <answer>continuous loads</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[voltage drop]]></answer>
        <answer>insulation</answer>
        <answer>wet locations</answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>The ampacity of a conductor can be different along the length of the conductor. The higher ampacity can be used beyond the point of transition for a distance of no more than _____ ft, or no more than _____ percent of the circuit length figured at the higher ampacity, whichever is less.</text>
        <showAfterPage>3</showAfterPage>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[10, 10]]></answer>
        <answer>10, 20</answer>
        <answer>15, 15</answer>
        <answer>20, 10</answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>There are four principal determinants of conductor operating temperature, one of which is _____ generated internally in the conductor as the result of load current flow.</text>
        <showAfterPage>4</showAfterPage>
        <answer>friction</answer>
        <answer>magnetism</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[heat]]></answer>
        <answer>none of these</answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>When correcting conductor ampacity for elevated ambient temperature, the correction factor [310.15(B)(2)(a)] used for THHN/THWN conductors is based on the _____ rating of the conductor in a dry location.</text>
        <showAfterPage>5</showAfterPage>
        <answer>75°C</answer>
        <answer>85°C</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[90°C]]></answer>
        <answer>95°C</answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>The ampacity adjustment factors of Table 310.15(B)(3)(a) does not apply to Type AC or Type MC cable without an overall outer jacket, if which of the following conditions are met?</text>
        <showAfterPage>6</showAfterPage>
        <answer>Each cable has not more than three current-carrying conductors.</answer>
        <answer>The conductors are 12 AWG copper.</answer>
        <answer>No more than 20 current-carrying conductors are installed without maintaining spacing.</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[all of these]]></answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>Where conductors or cables are installed in circular conduits exposed to direct sunlight on or above rooftops, the ambient temperature shall be increased by _____ where the conduits are less than 1/2 in. from the rooftop.</text>
        <showAfterPage>7</showAfterPage>
        <answer>30°F</answer>
        <answer>40°F</answer>
        <answer>50°F</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[60°F]]></answer>
      </question>
 
       <question>
        <text>Type NM and Type NMC cables shall be permitted in _____.</text>
        <showAfterPage>2</showAfterPage>
        <answer>in one- and two-family dwellings and their attached/detached garages or storage buildings</answer>
        <answer>multifamily dwellings permitted to be of Types III, IV, and V construction</answer>
        <answer>other structures permitted to be of Types III, IV, and V construction, except as prohibited in 334.12. </answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[any of these]]></answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>A detached residential garage isn’t a dwelling unit as defined in Article 100.</text>
        <showAfterPage>3</showAfterPage>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[True]]></answer>
        <answer>False</answer>
      </question>
 
      <question>
        <text>Snap switches are considered to be part of the effective ground-fault current path when _____.</text>
        <showAfterPage>2</showAfterPage>
        <answer>the switch is connected to the intersystem bonding termination</answer>
        <answer>the switch is mounted with metal screws to a metal box or a metal cover that’s connected to an equipment grounding conductor of a type recognized in 250.118</answer>
        <answer>an equipment grounding conductor or equipment bonding jumper is connected to the grounding terminal of the metal mounting yoke </answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[the switch is mounted with metal screws to a metal box or a metal cover that’s connected to an equipment grounding conductor of a type recognized in 250.118 or an equipment grounding conductor or equipment bonding jumper is connected to the grounding terminal of the metal mounting yoke ]]></answer>
      </question>
      <question>
        <text>A snap switch that does not have means for connection to an equipment grounding conductor shall be permitted for replacement purposes only where the wiring method does not include an equipment grounding conductor and the switch is _____.</text>
        <showAfterPage>3</showAfterPage>
        <answer>provided with a faceplate of nonconducting, noncombustible material with nonmetallic screws</answer>
        <answer>GFCI protected</answer>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[provided with a faceplate of nonconducting, noncombustible material with nonmetallic screws or GFCI protected]]></answer>
        <answer>none of these</answer>
      </question>
 
      <question>
        <text>All switchboards and panelboards supplied by a feeder in _____ shall be marked as to the device or equipment where the power supply originates.</text>
        <showAfterPage>2</showAfterPage>
        <answer correct="true"><![CDATA[other than one- or two-family dwellings]]></answer>
        <answer>all dwelling units</answer>
        <answer>all nondwelling units</answer>
        <answer>all dwelling units and all nondwelling units</answer>
      </question>
 
    <!--End Section-->
 
  <!--End Chapter-->
</course>